[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Fight Club character utters the line, have you ever heard a death rattle?", "correct_answer": "Marla", "incorrect_answers": ["Tyler", "Jack", "Chloe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The average person can live this number of days without water.", "correct_answer": "11", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "21", "31"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1905, this British scientist suggested the word genetics to describe the study of inheritance.", "correct_answer": "William Bateson", "incorrect_answers": ["Hennig Brand", "Karl Pearson", "Adam Sedgwick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Greek philosopher is known for writing about the fabled land of Atlantis.", "correct_answer": "Plato", "incorrect_answers": ["Socrates", "Homer", "Aristotle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During World War I approximately how many soldiers died as a result of avalanches?", "correct_answer": "60,000", "incorrect_answers": ["25,000", "10,000", "40,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American actress and stand-up comedian, host of a syndicated talk show, wrote an autobiography, entitled My Point...And I Do Have One.", "correct_answer": "Ellen DeGeneres", "incorrect_answers": ["Phyillis Diller", "Wanda Sykes", "Joan Rovers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the Freedom Trail begin and end?", "correct_answer": "Boston Common, Charlestown Navy Yard", "incorrect_answers": ["Kings Chapel, Bunker Hill Monument", "Trinity Church, Long Wharf", "Boston Public Gardens, Old North Church"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The two female cats that share Joe Greys talents at sleuthing are Dulce and this cat.", "correct_answer": "Kit", "incorrect_answers": ["Lovelylace", "Kaboodle", "Amelia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Russian astronaut became the first person to be married in space, while he was on the International Space Station?", "correct_answer": "Yuri Malenchenko", "incorrect_answers": ["Vladimir Dezhurov", "Yuri Gidzenko", "Sergei K. Krikalev"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why were Levis original blue jeans sewn with orange thread?", "correct_answer": "Because it matched the color of the copper rivets", "incorrect_answers": ["Because the orange thread was cheaper", "Because of the trademark color", "Because the orange thread was the strongest available"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When first announced, the RS MultiMediaCard (RS-MMC) was available in what maximum density?", "correct_answer": "64mb", "incorrect_answers": ["32mb", "128mb", "256mb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "North to the Future is the official motto of this US state, which is the largest in area.", "correct_answer": "Alaska", "incorrect_answers": ["Texas", "Nevada", "Colorado"]}]